{
    "subject": "resource/A._B._Masilamani",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#comment",
    "object": "Acharya A. B. Masilamani or Abel Boanerges Masilamani (1914-1990) (Telugu: \u0c0e\u0c2c\u0c46\u0c32\u0c4d \u0c2c\u0c4b\u0c28\u0c46\u0c30\u0c4d\u0c17\u0c46\u0c38\u0c4d \u0c2e\u0c3e\u0c38\u0c3f\u0c32\u0c3e\u0c2e\u0c23\u0c3f) was a Baptist Pastor and Evangelist ordained by the Convention of Baptist Churches of Northern Circars and Spiritual Formator from 1956-1959 at the Baptist Theological Seminary, a Major Seminary in Kakinada.",
    "human_readable": "The comment about Acharya A. B. Masilamani or Abel Boanerges Masilamani is Acharya A. B. Masilamani or Abel Boanerges Masilamani (1914-1990) (Telugu: \u0c0e\u0c2c\u0c46\u0c32\u0c4d \u0c2c\u0c4b\u0c28\u0c46\u0c30\u0c4d\u0c17\u0c46\u0c38\u0c4d \u0c2e\u0c3e\u0c38\u0c3f\u0c32\u0c3e\u0c2e\u0c23\u0c3f).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9222758412361145,
            "question": "Who was Acharya A. B. Masilamani?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9174320697784424,
            "question": "Was Acharya A. B. Masilamani known by two different names?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.903496265411377,
            "question": "What is another way to refer to Acharya A. B. Masilamani?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8982429504394531,
            "question": "What is the significance of the two names provided for Acharya A. B. Masilamani?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.89784836769104,
            "question": "What were the names used by Acharya A. B. Masilamani?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8823309540748596,
            "question": "When was Acharya A. B. Masilamani born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.869425892829895,
            "question": "How might knowing both names be helpful in understanding more about Acharya A. B. Masilamani?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8277201652526855,
            "question": "In what year did Acharya A. B. Masilamani pass away?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.685807466506958,
            "question": "Can you provide the birth and death years of Acharya A. B. Masilamani?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5809913277626038,
            "question": "What language is  '\u0c0e\u0c2c\u0c46\u0c32\u0c4d \u0c2c\u0c4b\u0c28\u0c46\u0c30\u0c4d\u0c17\u0c46\u0c38\u0c4d \u0c2e\u0c3e\u0c38\u0c3f\u0c32\u0c3e\u0c2e\u0c23\u0c3f' written in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The comment about Acharya A. B. Masilamani or Abel Boanerges Masilamani is Acharya A. B. Masilamani or Abel Boanerges Masilamani (1914-1990) (Telugu: \u0c0e\u0c2c\u0c46\u0c32\u0c4d \u0c2c\u0c4b\u0c28\u0c46\u0c30\u0c4d\u0c17\u0c46\u0c38\u0c4d \u0c2e\u0c3e\u0c38\u0c3f\u0c32\u0c3e\u0c2e\u0c23\u0c3f).",
            "html": "dbpedia_9266_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide the birth and death years of Acharya A. B. Masilamani?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9266_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Acharya A. B. Masilamani pass away?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9266_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How might knowing both names be helpful in understanding more about Acharya A. B. Masilamani?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9266_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9266_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9266_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9266_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9266_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9266_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9266_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9266_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9266_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9266_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9266_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple:\n\nAcharya A. B. Masilamani or Abel Boanerges Masilamani is (1914-1990).\n\nThis can be inferred from the following sentence in the first document:\n\n\"Acharya A. B. Masilamani or Abel Boanerges Masilamani (1914\u20131990) was a Golden Jubilee Baptist pastor and evangelist...\"\n\nAnd also from the second document which mentions his date of birth as 1914, but does not mention his year of death. However, in the context of the other dates mentioned in the text, it can be inferred that he passed away in 1990."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided context does include information about Acharya A. B. Masilamani or Abel Boanerges Masilamani, specifying his lifespan as (1914\u20131990), which aligns with the given statement: \"Acharya A. B. Masilamani or Abel Boanerges Masilamani (1914-1990) (Telugu: \u0c0e\u0c2c\u0c46\u0c32\u0c4d \u0c2c\u0c4b\u0c28\u0c46\u0c30\u0c4d\u0c17\u0c46\u0c38\u0c4d \u0c2e\u0c3e\u0c38\u0c3f\u0c32\u0c3e\u0c2e\u0c23\u0c3f)\"."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}